Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) Records
Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) Records
1951-2008
1955-1975
Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education.
19 linear ft.
Material collected or published by Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE). Publications include original monographs as well as works from the Clearinghouse of Resources for Educators of Adults, Fund for Adult Education, the International Seminar on Adult Education, the Center for the Study of Liberal Education for Adults, ERIC, American Foundation for Continuing Education, the Library of Continuing Education at Syracuse University, and miscellaneous publications by notable adult educators including Alexander N. Charters, Cyril O. Houle, J. Roby Kidd, A.A. Liveright, John Ohliger, James B. Whipple, et al. There are also three boxes of administrative files.
148693
Biographical History
In 1969 the Ford Foundation approved a five-year grant to Syracuse University for the continued availability, distribution, and servicing of materials developed by the American Foundation for Continuing Education and the Center for the Study of Liberal Education for Adults, both former grantees of the Ford Foundation's Fund for Adult Education. Prior to that, in 1950, University College (UC) of Syracuse University (SU) had published a series of "blue books" in the field; the University's Library of Continuing Education (LCE) developed and published a number of works in the 1960s; and ERIC initiated documents, which the University had published alone or in cooperation with other institutions. All began to be collected under the general rubric of SUPCE, along with significant works by prominent adult educators and material published by other adult education organizations such as the Fund for Adult Education. Doris Chertow served as the editor for the publications under SU's Vice President for Continuing Education, Alexander N. Charters.
Although SUPCE's federal funding ended in 1975, it continued to release updates to original SUPCE publications as well as publishing the occasional new monograph under its own name and, later, under the auspices of the Academic Institute for Educators of Adults (AIEA) within the School of Education at Syracuse University, until 2008.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) Records consists of a near-complete set of all material collected or published by SUPCE, along with drafts of some items and some administrative files for both SUPCE and Syracuse Resources for Educators of Adults (SUREA). Individuals well-known in the field of adult education represented in the collection include Robert J. Blakely, Alexander N. Charters, Roger DeCrow, Cyril O. Houle, J. Roby Kidd, A. A. (Alexander Albert) Liveright, Paul H. Sheats, John Ohliger, and James B. Whipple.
Drafts, notes and galleys contains pre-publication versions of a few SUPCE publications.
Publications contains a nearly-complete set of all items published, reprinted, or collected by SUPCE over the course of its existence. Although SUPCE's federal funding ended in 1975, updates to many of its publications as well as the occasional new SUPCE monograph have been released on an irregular basis over the years, under the auspices of the Academic Institute for Educators of Adults (AIEA) within the school of education at Syracuse University. The publications are divided into several subseries which are arranged alphabetically; individual items are in numerical order by their three-letter code.
Note that several of the MSS subseries documents contain lists of SUPCE publications or resources. These were accurate at the time of compilation but naturally may have since been superseded; this finding aid comprises the most complete and current listing. Because a complete list of SUPCE materials does not exist elsewhere, we have taken the unusual step of making the list given here in the finding aid complete, despite the fact that the collection itself is not. Items missing from the collection are indicated by the notation "[MISSING]" immediately following the three-letter code and preceding the title of the item. As of August 2006, Box 9 was missing. All items in that box are therefore marked as [MISSING].
Administrative files and SUREA comprise office files pertaining to the operation of these two organizations, including correspondence, financial records, order logs, and more.
Arrangement of the Collection
Material is sorted alphabetically by SUPCE's three-letter codes, and within that titles are listed numerically.
Other Formats Available
Many of the MSS series documents have been digitized and are available online. To view these document, please click here.
Related Material
The library holds a considerable number of collections related to adult and continuing education. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Adult education; Blakely, Robert J.; Charters, Alexander N.; Chertow, Doris.; DeCrow, Roger.; Houle, Cyril Orvin, 1913-; Kidd, J. R. (James Robbins), 1915-1982.; Liveright, A. A. (Alexander Albert), 1907-; Sheats, Paul H., 1907-; Ohliger, John.; Whipple, James B.; International Seminar on Adult Education.; American Foundation for Continuing Education.; Center for the Study of Liberal Education for Adults.; Fund for Adult Education (U.S.); Adult education.; Educational publishing.; Bibliographies.; Drafts (documents); Essays.; Monographs.; Pamphlets.; Reports.; Educators.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Inventory
- Drafts, notes and galleys
  - AFC48 Science and Public Policy (AFCE/Oceana), 7 folders (Box 1)
    See also Publications: American Foundation for Continuing Education (AFCE) series (AFC): AFC48 Science and Public Policy (AFCE/Oceana)
  - LNH2 The Cooperative Extension Service: Paradoxical Servant (Miller, Paul A.) (Box 1)
    See also Publications: Landmark and New Horizons series (LNH): LNH2 The Cooperative Extension Service: Paradoxical Servant
  - NES59 The System of Adult Education in Yugoslavia (Savicevic, Dusan M.) (Box 2)
    See also Publications: Notes and Essays and Reports in Continuing Education for Adults series (NES): NES59 The System of Adult Education in Yugoslavia
  - NES60 Liberal Education Reconsidered: Reflections on Continuing Education for Contemporary Man (Whipple, James B. Goldman, Freda H. Haygood, Kenneth Siegle, Peter) (Box 2)
    See also Publications: Notes and Essays and Reports in Continuing Education for Adults series (NES): NES60 Liberal Education Reconsidered: Reflections on Continuing Education for Contemporary Man
  - NES61 Aim: From Concept to Reality (Wedemeyer, Charles A. Najem, Robert E.), 2 folders (Box 2)
    See also Publications: Notes and Essays and Reports in Continuing Education for Adults series (NES): NES61 Aim: From Concept to Reality
  - NES62 Dilemmas of American Policy: Crucial Issues in Contemporary Society (Cook, Samuel Dubois Stern, George G. Green, Thomas F. Weiner, Anthony J.), 5 folders (Box 2, 3)
    See also Publications: Notes and Essays and Reports in Continuing Education for Adults series (NES): NES62 Dilemmas of American Policy: Crucial Issues in Contemporary Society
  - NES63 Knowledge is Power to Control Power (Blakely, Robert Lappin, I.), 2 folders (Box 3)
    See also Publications: Notes and Essays and Reports in Continuing Education for Adults series (NES): NES63 Knowledge is Power to Control Power
  - NES64 The University and Community Service (Whipple, James B. Chertow, Doris), 2 folders (Box 3)
    See also Publications: Notes and Essays and Reports in Continuing Education for Adults series (NES): NES64 The University and Community Service
  - NES65 Essays on New Careers: Social Implications for Adult Educators (Riessman, Frank Rosen, Sumner M. Featherstone, Joseph Gartner, Alan), 8 folders (Box 4)
    See also Publications: Notes and Essays and Reports in Continuing Education for Adults series (NES): NES65 Essays on New Careers: Social Implications for Adult Educators
  - NES66 Essays on the Future of Continuing Education Worldwide (Ziegler, Warren), 2 folders (Box 4)
    See also Publications: Notes and Essays and Reports in Continuing Education for Adults series (NES): NES66 Essays on the Future of Continuing Education Worldwide
  - NES69 Ends and Means: The National Conference on Continuing Education in Nursing (McHenry, Ruth W.) (Box 4)
    See also Publications: Notes and Essays and Reports in Continuing Education for Adults series (NES): NES69 Ends and Means: The National Conference on Continuing Education in Nursing
  - NES70 Residential Continuing Education (Houle, Cyril O.) (Box 5)
    See also Publications: Notes and Essays and Reports in Continuing Education for Adults series (NES): NES70 Residential Continuing Education
  - NES71 Selected Concepts from Educational Psychology and Adult Education for Extension and Continuing Educators (Leagans, J. Paul Copeland, Harlan G. Kaiser, Gertrude E.) (Box 5)
    See also Publications: Notes and Essays and Reports in Continuing Education for Adults series (NES): NES71 Selected Concepts from Educational Psychology and Adult Education for Extension and Continuing Educators
  - OCP19 Accent on Adults: The Small College Program at Brooklyn (Jacobson, Myrtle S. Offenbacher, Deborah I.) (Box 5)
    See also Publications: Occasional Papers (CSLEA) series (OCP): OCP19 Accent on Adults: The Small College Program at Brooklyn
  - OCP20 Faculty Perceptions of Continuing Education at Syracuse University (Porter, Lee) (Box 5)
    See also Publications: Occasional Papers (CSLEA) series (OCP): OCP20 Faculty Perceptions of Continuing Education at Syracuse University
  - OCP21 Community Service and Continuing Education (Whipple, James B.) (Box 5)
    See also Publications: Occasional Papers (CSLEA) series (OCP): OCP21 Community Service and Continuing Education
  - OCP22 Adult Education and the Disadvantaged Adult (Anderson, Darrel Niemi, John) (Box 5)
    See also Publications: Occasional Papers (CSLEA) series (OCP): OCP22 Adult Education and the Disadvantaged Adult
  - OCP24 Lifelong Learning or Lifelong Schooling: A Tentative View of the Ideas of Ivan Illich (Ohliger, John McCarthy, C.) (Box 5)
    See also Publications: Occasional Papers (CSLEA) series (OCP): OCP24 Lifelong Learning or Lifelong Schooling: A Tentative View of the Ideas of Ivan Illich
  - OCP25 The Learning Force: A More Comprehensive Framework for Educational Policy (Moses, Stanley) (Box 5)
    See also Publications: Occasional Papers (CSLEA) series (OCP): OCP25 The Learning Force: A More Comprehensive Framework for Educational Policy
- Publications
  - American Foundation for Continuing Education (AFCE) series (AFC)
    - AFC1 Economics and Politics (Harlan, H. C.), 1958 (Box 6)
    - AFC2 Readings in World Politics v. 1-4, plus Discussion Leader's Manual, 1951 (Box 6)
    - AFC3 Readings in World Politics v. 1-3, 2nd edition, 1953 (Box 6)
    - AFC4 Readings in World Politics, Vol. 1, 2 (Goldwin, Robert A. and Lerner, Ralph; Stourzh, Gerald), 1957 (Box 6)
    - AFC5 Readings in World Politics, Session Guides (Staff, American Foundation for Political Education), 1957 (Box 6)
    - AFC6 Readings in World Politics, Sessions 1 and 2 (Staff, American Foundation for Political Education), 1957 (Box 6)
    - AFC7 Readings in World Politics, Discussion Leader's Manual (Staff, American Foundation for Political Education), 1955 (Box 6)
    - AFC8 Readings in Russian Foreign Policy, Vol. 1 and Vol. 2, 2d Edition (Goldwin, Robert A. and Zetterbaum, Marvin), 1953 (Box 6)
    - AFC9 Readings in Russian Foreign Policy, Vol. 1 and Vol. 2, 3rd Edition (Goldwin, Robert A. and Zetterbaum, Marvin), 1953 (Box 6)
    - AFC10 Readings in Russian Foreign Policy, Sessions 8 & 9 (Staff, American Foundation for Political Education), 1957 (Box 6)
    - AFC11 The Russian Foreign Policy Program, Discussion Leader's Manual (Zetterbaum, Marvin), 1957 (Box 6)
    - AFC12 Readings in Russian Foreign Policy, Supplement; Tables and Maps (Goldwin, Robert A. and Zetterbaum, Marvin), 1953 (Box 6)
    - AFC13 Readings in American Democracy, Vol. 1 and 2 (Stourzh, Gerald and Lerner, Ralph), 1957 (Box 6)
    - AFC14 [MISSING] Readings in American Democracy, Sessions 1 & 2 (Staff, American Foundation for Political Education) (Box 6)
    - AFC15 A Statement Concerning the American Foundation for Political Education (Staff), 1953 (Box 6)
    - AFC16 Annual Report of Ex. Director Year ending March 31, American Foundation for Political Education (Nelson, Charles E.) (Box 6)
    - AFC17 Annual Report of Ex. Director Year ending June 30, American Foundation for Political Education (Nelson, Charles E.) (Box 6)
    - AFC18 American Foundation for Political Education, A Statement - Including Annual Report of Exec. Director - Year ending June 30, 1955 (Nelson, Charles E.), 1956 (Box 6)
    - AFC19 American Foundation for Political Education, A Statement - Including Annual Report of Exec. Director - Year Ending June 30, 1956 (Ziegler, Jerome M.) (Box 6)
    - AFC20 American Foundation for Political Education, Annual Report - Year ending June 30, 1957 (Ziegler, Jerome M.), 1958 (Box 6)
    - AFC21 American Foundation for Continuing Education, 2 Year Report - Period ending June 30, 1959 (Ziegler, Jerome) (Box 6)
    - AFC22 [MISSING] American Foundation for Continuing Education, Programs and Publications (Williams, Harold S.) (Box 6)
    - AFC23 American Foundations for Continuing Education, Programs and Publications (Williams, Harold S.) (Box 6)
    - AFC24 [MISSING] The American Foreign Policy Program, Discussion Leader's Manual (Goldwin, Robert A.), 1955 (Box 6)
    - AFC25 [MISSING] Readings in American Foreign Policy (Goldwin, Robert A. and Stourzh, Gerald) 6th edition, 1958; Vol. I - Sessions 1-5 Vol. II - Sessions 6-8 (Box 9)
    - AFC26 [MISSING] Readings in American Foreign Policy (Goldwin, Robert A.) 4th edition, 1955; Vol. 1 - Sessions 1-4 Vol. 2 - Sessions 5-7 Vol. 3 - Sessions 8-10 (Box 9)
    - AFC27 [MISSING] Readings for Men & Labor (Fertig, Ralph D.), 1962 (Box 9)
    - AFC28 Readings for Peace Corps Trainees, nos. 1-5, 8-10 (Christensen, David; University of Chicago), 1966; 8 folders (Box 6)
      Vol. I - The Peace Corps: Missionary Society's Peace Army or What?
      Vol. II - Cultural Confrontation:Terrifying and Illuminating
      Vol. III - Freedom Round or Freedom Square
      Vol. IV - On the Making of Volunteers
      Vol. V - Of Gifts and Bribes and Stones that Cry
      Vol VIII - Varieties of Cannibalism
      Vol. IX - Bringing It All Back Home
      Vol. X - Where Has It Been and Where Is It Going?
    - AFC29 [MISSING] Ways to Justice (Sinclair, Lister), 1954 (Box 9)
    - AFC30[MISSING] Jefferson and Our Times (Malone, Dumas), 1955 (Box 9)
    - AFC31 [MISSING] Jeffersonian Heritage (Malone, Dumas), 1955 (Box 9)
    - AFC32 [MISSING] Introduction to the Humanities (record album) (Box 9)
    - AFC33 [MISSING] Great Issues in American Politics Part I (Hofstadter, Richard), 1956 (Box 9)
      See also Administrative files: "Great Issues in American Politics"
    - AFC34 [MISSING] The Power to Govern: An Examination of the Separation of Powers in the American System of Government (Odegard, Peter H. and Rosenblum, Victor G.), 1957 (Box 9)
    - AFC35 [MISSING] Economics and Politics: A Book of Readings (Harlan, H. C.), 1958 (Box 9)
    - AFC36 [MISSING] Arms and Foreign Policy in the Nuclear Age (Rakove, Milton), 1964 (Box 9)
    - AFC37 [MISSING] Developing Responsible Public Leaders (Nelson, Charles A.) (Box 9)
    - AFC38 [MISSING] The Case of the Lively Ghost (Goldwin, Robert A. and Shoemaker, Don), 1956 (Box 9)
    - AFC39 [MISSING] The Case of the Toppling Idol (Stourzh, Gerald), 1956 (Box 9)
    - AFC40 [MISSING] The Case of the Lengthening Chain (Steward, Jr., Charles K. and Goldwin, Robert A.), 1959 (Box 9)
    - AFC41 [MISSING] The Case of the Blighted City (Banfield, Edward C.), 1959 (Box 9)
    - AFC42 [MISSING] The Case of the Censored Librarian (Berns, Walter F.), 1959 (Box 9)
    - AFC43 [MISSING] The Case of the Golden Door (Davidson, James F.), 1960 (Box 9)
    - AFC44, 45, 46 [MISSING] Readings for Capitol Hill, Vols. 1, 2, 3 (Ziegler, Warren L.), 1963 (Box 9)
    - AFC47 [MISSING] Exploring the Universe (McGraw-Hill), 1963 (Box 9)
    - AFC48 [MISSING] Science and Public Policy (AFCE/Oceana), 1970 (Box 9)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: AFC48 Science and Public Policy (AFCE/Oceana)
    - AFC49 [MISSING] The Exploration of the Universe (AFCE), 1962 (Box 9)
    - AFC50 [MISSING] Democracy in America: Scripts of the Fourteen Dramatizations (with National Educational Television Radio Center) (Sinclair, Lister and Probst, George E.), 1962 (Box 9)
    - AFC51 [MISSING] The Happy Republic (Probst, George E., ed.; Harper Torchbooks), 1962 (Box 9)
    - AFC52 [MISSING] Democracy in America: Vols. 1 & 2 (de Tocqueville, Alexis; Vintage Books and Schocken Books), 1962 (Box 9)
    - AFC53 [MISSING] Democracy in America: Laden's Discussion and Reading Guide (Probst, George E.), 1962 (Box 9)
    - AFC54 [MISSING] Democracy in America: Discussion and Reading Guide (for students and discussion participants) (Probst, George E.), 1962 (Box 9)
    - AFC55 [MISSING] Readings in American Foreign Policy (Stourzh, Gerald and Goldwin, Robert A.), 1959 (Box 9)
    - AFC55A [MISSING] Readings in American Foreign Policy, second edition (Goldwin, Robert A. and Clar, Harry M.), 1971 (Box 9)
    - AFC56 [MISSING] Readings in Russian Foreign Policy (Stourzh, Gerald and Zetterbaum, Marvin, eds)., 1959 (Box 9)
    - AFC57 Exploring the Ways of Mankind (book) (Goldschmidt, Walter, editor), 1960 (Box 6)
    - AFC58 Aging in Today's Society (Tibbits, Clark and Donahue, Wilma), 1960 (Box 6)
    - AFC59 Discovering Modern Poetry (Drew, Elizabeth and Conner, George), 1961 (Box 6)
    - AFC60 The Mystery of Matter, Vol. 1 (Young, Louise B.), 1963 (Box 6)
    - AFC61 [MISSING] The Mystery of Matter, Vol. 2 (Young, Louise B.), 1962 (Box 7)
    - AFC62 [MISSING] The Mystery of Matter, Vol. 3 (Young, Louise B.), 1962 (Box 7)
    - AFC62A The Mystery of Matter (Young, Louise B.), 1965 (Box 7)
    - AFC63 Discussion Leader's Guide for Use with Discovering Modern Poetry (Drew, Elizabeth and Conner, George), 1961 (Box 7)
    - AFC64 [MISSING] Reading in Economics and Politics (Harlan, H. C.; Galbraith, Kenneth; Lerner, Max; Nixon, Richard; Kennan, George, editors), 1966 (Box 7)
    - AFC65 Readings in American Democracy (Stourzh, Gerald and Lerner, Ralph, eds), 1966 (Box 7)
    - AFC66 Ten Major Issues in American Politics (Hofstadter, Richard), 1968 (Box 7)
    - AFC67 Readings in World Politics (Pearce, Anthony; Oxford Press), 1970 (Box 7)
    - AFC68 Evolution of Man (Young, Louise B., ed.), 1970 (Box 7)
      See also Administrative: "Evolution of Man" - correspondence; Administrative: "Evolution of Man" - contract agreement
    - AFC69 Readings on Drug Education (Reagen, Michael V., ed.), 1972 (Box 7)
    - AFC70 [MISSING] The Citizen and the New Age of Science, Vol. 1 (Box 7)
    - AFC71 Advanced Management Training Workbook (Box 7)
  - Syracuse University Centennial series (CEN)
    - CEN1 [MISSING] Continuing Education Programs #1 (Charters, Alexander N., ed.), 1971 (Box 7)
    - CEN2 Bureau of School Service #2 (Charters, Alexander N., ed.), 1970 (Box 7)
    - CEN3 Division of International Programs Abroad #3 (Charters, Alexander N., ed.), 1970 (Box 7)
    - CEN4 Division of Summer Sessions #4 (Charters, Alexander N., ed.) (Box 7)
    - CEN5 ERIC Clearinghouse on Adult Education #5 (Charters, Alexander N.) (Box 7)
    - CEN6 International Management Development Department (Charters, Alexander N.), 1970 (Box 7)
    - CEN7 Library of Continuing Education #7 (Charters, Alexander N., ed.), 1970 (Box 7)
    - CEN8 Archives of Continuing Education #717A (Charters, Alexander N., ed.) (Box 7)
    - CEN9 Professional Development in Adult and Continuing Education (Charters, Alexander N., ed.), 1970 (Box 7)
    - CEN10 Publications in Continuing Education #9 (Charters, Alexander N., ed.) (Box 7)
    - CEN11 Research, Evaluation, and Planning in Adult and Continuing Education #10 (Charters, Alexander N., ed.), 1970 (Box 7)
    - CEN12 This is U.C. #11 (Charters, Alexander N., ed.), 1970 (Box 7)
  - Clearinghouse of Resources for Educators of Adults (CREA) series (CRE)
    - CRE1 Acquisition List, Clearinghouse of Resources for Educators of Adults: by Descriptive Subject Headings (Charters, Alexander N. and Holmwood, Donald P.) (Box 7)
    - CRE2 Newsletters, Clearinghouse of Resources for Educators of Adults (Charters, Alexander N. and Holmwood, Donald P.), 1978 (Box 7)
    - CRE3 Professional Development for Educators of Adults: A Bibliography (Charters, Alexander N. and Holmwood, Donald P. Compilers), 1977 (Box 7)
    - CRE4 Annotated Bibliography for the Education of Public Offenders: By Descriptive Subject Headings (Charters, Alexander N. and Holmwood, Donald P. Willis, Michael J.) (Box 7)
    - CRE5 Community Education: An Annotated Bibliography (Charters, Alexander N. and Gschwender, Edward J.), 1979 (Box 7)
    - CRE6 Literacy in the '70s: An Annotated Bibliography (Rivera, W. and Laubach, Robert S.), 1980 (Box 8)
  - Distributing Agent series (DAG)
    - DAG1 Strategies for Lifelong learning (Himmelstrup, Per, et al., ed.), 1981 (Box 8)
  - Eric Clearinghouse on Adult Education series (ECA)
    - ECA1 Evening College Education, 1967 (Box 8)
    - ECA2 Higher Adult Education #1, 1967 (Box 8)
    - ECA3 [MISSING] Community Education for Adults, 1967 (Box 8)
    - ECA4 Adult Basic Education, 1967 (Box 8)
    - ECA5 Continuing Education in the Professions, 1967 (Box 8)
    - ECA6 Management Development, 1967 (Box 8)
    - ECA7 Television and Radio in Adult Education, 1967 (Box 8)
    - ECA8 Methods and Techniques in Adult Training, 1967 (Box 8)
    - ECA9 Training of Adult Education Personnel, 1967 (Box 8)
    - ECA10 Public School Adult Education, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA11 Human Relations-Training and Research, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECAl2 Higher Adult Education #2, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA13 Adult Education in Africa, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA14 Adult Education in Asia, Australia and New Zealand, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA15 Education for Aging, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA16 Programmed Instruction in Adult Education, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA17 Community Education for Adults, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA18 Management Development, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA19 Adult Basic Education, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA20 Public School Adult Education, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA21 Adult Learning Characteristics, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA22 Continuing Education of Women, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA23 Counseling and Personnel Services in Adult Education: Counseling, Testing, Selection, Retention (Glick, Barry, ed.), 1969 (Box 8)
    - ECA24 [MISSING] Unknown (Box 8)
    - ECA25 Residential Adult Education, 1969; 300+ pages, available on microfilm only. MICROFILM #2973. (Box 8)
    - ECA26 Management and Supervisory Development, 1969 (Box 8)
    - ECA27 Adult Basic Education, 1970 (Box 8)
    - ECA28 Programmed Instruction in Business and Industry, 1970 (Box 8)
    - ECA29 Occupational Training for Disadvantaged Adults, 1970 (Box 8)
    - ECA30 Parent, Home and Family Life Education, 1970 (Box 8)
    - ECA31 Personnel Development in Adult Education, 1970 (Box 8)
    - ECA32 Continuing Education of Women, 1970 (Box 8)
    - ECA33 [MISSING] Training of Law Enforcement Personnel, 1971 (Box 8)
    - ECA34 [MISSING] Methods and Techniques of Adult Training (Box 8)
    - ECA35 Cooperative Extension, 1968 (Box 8)